<resources>

    <string name="action_settings">Map</string>

    <string name="principal">Homepage</string>
    <string name="title_activity_vista_activity">Tourism El Retiro v2.1</string>
    <string name="hoteles">Hotels</string>
    <string name="bares">Restaurants and Bars</string>
    <string name="sitios_turisticos">Turist Places</string>
    <string name="demografia">Demographics</string>
    <string name="acercade">About</string>

    <string name="app_name">Tourism El Retiro v2.1</string>
    <string name="principal_intro">El Retiro is known as the "Cradle of Liberty" because it was there that the first release of slaves in the country was held in 1789.
    The architecture of traditional village that preserves El Retiro and its rich history make it a very attractive place interesting.</string>
    <string name="principal_intro2">Go and knows the tradition of cabinetmakers working families with wood perfection; you can take to acquire various objects in this material.</string>
    <string name="principal_intro3">It is reached by the Via Las Palmas is just 40 minutes from Medellin.</string>
    <string name="distancia">Distance: 32 km</string>
    <string name="temp">Temperature: 16°C</string>
    <string name="altura">Height: 2.175 m</string>

    <string name="title_activity_hoteles">Hotels</string>
    <string name="la_antigua">La Antigua</string>
    <string name="la_antigua_info">The Hotel La Antigua is located in the exclusive historic area of El Retiro. Located approximately 33 kilometers from the city of Medellin, and between this city
    and the municipalities of Rionegro and La Ceja. This region is architecturally the most traditional for its surroundings between town and country, with roads dual carriageway for a comfortable journey.</string>
    <string name="la_antigua_info2"> Cra. 21 N° 21 – 49 - El Retiro, Antioquia</string>
    <string name="chaparral">El Chaparral</string>
    <string name="chaparral_info">10 guest cabins each with private bathroom services with hot water, minibar, cable TV and personalized service to the room, with great variety of grilled meats charcoal
    and firewood, and a variety of spirits, athletic activities fishing, horse rental and games for children.</string>
    <string name="chaparral_info2">Kilometer 2 way la fe, El Retiro</string>
    <string name="cabrero">El Cabrero</string>
    <string name="cabrero_info">El Cabrero is located 15 km from the center of El Retiro. El Cabrero has 16 rooms with private bathroom and free internet. El Cabrero has a fully equipped kitchen, living room
    and terrace with wonderful lake view. El Cabrero organizes activities like hiking in the different surroundings.</string>

    <string name="title_activity_bares">Restaurants y Bars</string>
    <string name="deleite">Deleite - Comidas Bar</string>
    <string name="deleite_info">Street 19 # 20 – 11 Principal park</string>
    <string name="guarceño">El Pilón Guarceño</string>
    <string name="guarceño_info">Principal park</string>
    <string name="serenata">Serenata Paisa</string>
    <string name="serenata_info">La Fe Sector, Km 29 (Las Palmas)</string>

    <string name="title_activity_sitios_turisticos">Turistics Places</string>
    <string name="parquerepresa">Los Salados Park , La Fe Reservoir</string>
    <string name="parquerepresa_info">The center of activities is the dam of La Fe to which have been added several attractions for your entertainment.
    This park offers water bicycle, area restaurants, stands with grills, train, swimming, nature trails and other playground in a pleasant natural environment.</string>
    <string name="parquerepresa_info2">It is located on the edge of the road on the road linking Las Palmas Medellin with El Retiro.</string>
    <string name="tequendamita">El Tequendamita</string>
    <string name="tequendamita_info">It is an attractive crystalline water that takes its name from the similarity to the Tequendama Falls near Bogota, though much smaller.
    Admire its waterfall of over 20 meters high, formed by the stream Don Diego.</string>
    <string name="tequendamita_info2">It is 7 kilometers from the road to La Ceja.</string>
    <string name="iglesia">Church Nuestra Señora del Rosario</string>
    <string name="iglesia_info">The structure of this temple was completed in 1774. In the inner dome protruding altar paintings of the Evangelists San Juan, San Marcos, San Lucas and San Mateo.</string>
    <string name="reserva">Ecological reserve San Sebastián La Castellana</string>
    <string name="reserva_info">It is a complex of seven viewpoints, from where you can see a beautiful view of the Aburrá Valley, the Valley of San Nicholas and on sunny days, some mountains
    of Caldas, the Nevado del Ruiz and stone Guatapé.Cuenta with a wide variety of guaduales, flora and fauna, and a strip of cloud forest that add charm to the place.</string>
    <string name="reserva_info2">It is 13 km on the road to Medellin, taking a shortcut in the subdivision gate of Las Flores.</string>

    <string name="title_activity_demografia">Demographics</string>
    <string name="poblacion">Population</string>
    <string name="poblacion2">Total: 17.858 hab. (2009)</string>
    <string name="urbana">Town: 8.838</string>
    <string name="rural">Rural: 9.020</string>
    <string name="alfabetismo">Literacy</string>
    <string name="alfatotal">Total: 93.1% (2005)</string>
    <string name="alfaurbano">Town: 95.3%</string>
    <string name="alfarural">Rural: 90.9%</string>
    <string name="etnografia">Ethnography</string>
    <string name="etno">According to figures presented by DANE Census 2005:</string>
    <string name="mestizos">Mestizos and Whites: 99.9%</string>
    <string name="afros">Afro: 0.1%</string>

    <string name="title_activity_acercade">About</string>
    <string name="acerdade_intro1">Tourism El Retiro v2.1</string>
    <string name="acerdade_intro2">Application by:</string>
    <string name="acerdade_intro3">Jose Vargas</string>
    <string name="acerdade_intro4">University of Antioquia</string>
    <string name="acerdade_intro5">2015</string>


</resources>
